I killed Sirius Black!
He's back.
The police are continuing their investigation...
...into the disaster at the Millennium Bridge.
Traffic has been stopped while
the police search for survivors.
The area remains closed.
The Mayor has asked Londoners
to remain calm...
...as the investigation continues.
FALLEN FROM GRACE
MRS. AND MR. MALFOY'S SON
AND WIFE LEAVE THE COURT
"Harry Potter".
Who's Harry Potter?
Nobody.
Actually, he's a bit of an idiot.
Funny that newspaper.
I could have sworn I saw a picture move
a few nights ago.
- Really?
- I thought I was going mad.
- Hey. I was wondering--
- Eleven. That's when I leave.
You can tell me all about
that idiot Harry Potter.
You've been reckless this summer, Harry.
I like to travel by train.
It makes my mind wander.
To not very pleasant things, eh?
The story's exciting,
if I tell it to myself.
But now's not the time
to tell it.
Take my arm.